const STORE = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What type of bicycle should you use to commute?",
        answers: [
            "Full suspension mountain bike.",
            "E-bike.",
            "Hybrid on-road/off-road bike.",
            "Whatever bike you're comfortable with."
        ],
        correct: 3,
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What types of weather should you ride in?",
        answers: [
            "Sunshine.",
            "Darkness.",
            "Rain.",
            "Snow.",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        correct: 4,
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What tools do you need?",
        answers: [
            "Bell, horn, and other noise makers.",
            "The entire workshop.",
            "Spandex suit, reflective vest, race numbers.",
            "Tire levers, spare tube, multi-tool and an air pump."
        ],
        correct: 3,
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Where is it legal to ride?",
        answers: [
            "Anywhere a car can drive, plus bike lanes.",
            "Sidewalks and bridges.",
            "As far to the right as you can get and nowhere else.",
            "Down the median."
        ],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "How often should you get your bike checked?",
        answers: [
            "Every week.",
            "Every month.",
            "Every 6 months.",
            "Every year."
        ],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "When should you use your bike lights?",
        answers: [
            "All the time.",
            "When you want to be seen better.",
            "Nighttime only.",
            "Never."
        ],
        correct: 1,
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "How should you treat other cyclists?",
        answers: [
            "RACE THEM EVERYWHERE!",
            "Avoid them at all costs.",
            "Reach out and be friendly - it's a jungle out there.",
            "Imagine they don't exist."
        ],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "What type of bike lock is best?",
        answers: [
            "No lock needed, bikes are never stolen.",
            "A U-lock and possibly a cable lock for the tires.",
            "A combination lock.",
            "Chain and padlock."
        ],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "How should you signal to drivers?",
        answers: [
            "With your middle finger.",
            "Point where you are about to go unless unsafe to do so.",
            "No signaling is needed.",
            "With clothes that say \"I'm cool\"."
        ],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Bicycle commuting is:",
        answers: [
           "A great way to stay fit.",
           "A way of life.",
           "Road-rage free.",
           "All of the above."
        ],
        correct: 3
    }
]